<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HIITApp</string>
    <string name="burpees">Burpees</string>
    <string name="high_knees">High Knees</string>
    <string name="mountain_climbers">Mountain Climbers</string>
    <string name="pushups">Push-Ups</string>
    <string name="bicycle_crunch">Bicycle Crunch</string>
    <string name="planks">Planks</string>
    <string name="squats">Squats</string>
    <string name="donkey_kick">Donkey Kicks</string>
    <string name="leg_lifts">Leg Lifts</string>
    <string name="fire_hydrant">Fire Hydrants</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hiitexercises">HIITExercises</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="home_fragment">HOME</string>
    <string name="timer_fragment">TIMER</string>
    <string name="progress_fragment">PROGRESS</string>
    <string name="large_text">LARGE TEXT</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="progress">Progress</string>
    <string name="timer">Timer</string>
    <string name="pick_time">Pick a Time</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="set">Set</string>

    <string-array name="exercises">
        <item>Burpees</item>
        <item>High Knees</item>
        <item>Mountain Climbers</item>
        <item>Push-Ups</item>
        <item>Bicycle Crunch</item>
        <item>Planks</item>
        <item>Squats</item>
        <item>Donkey Kicks</item>
        <item>Back Leg Lifts</item>
        <item>Fire Hydrant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="burpees_desc">1. Stand straight with your feet shoulder-width apart.\n
2. Squat and place your hands in front of your feet.\n
3. Jump back until your legs are fully extended and your body is in plank position.\n
4. Do a push up, jump forward, and then push through the heels to return to the starting position.\n
5. Repeat until the set is complete.</string>

    <string name="high_knees_desc">1. Stand straight with your feet shoulder-width apart. Face forward and open your chest.\n
2. Bring your knees up to waist level and then slowly land on the balls of your feet.\n
3. Repeat until the set is complete.</string>

    <string name="mountain_climbers_desc">1. Start with your body in a straight line and your hands slightly wider than shoulder-width apart. Keep your toes and balls of the feet touching the floor.\n
2. Bring one knee up toward the center of your stomach and then quickly alternate between legs.\n
3. Continue alternating until the set is complete.</string>

    <string name="pushups_desc">1. With your legs extended back, place the hands below the shoulders, slightly wider than shoulder-width apart.\n
2. Start bending your elbows and lower your chest until it’s just above the floor.\n
3. Push back to the starting position. A 1-second push, 1-second pause, 2-second down count is ideal.\n
4. Repeat.</string>

    <string name="bicycle_crunch_desc">1. Lie on your back, lift your shoulders off the mat and raise both legs.\n
2. Bring one knee and the opposing elbow close to each other by crunching to one side, and fully extend the other leg.\n
3. Return to the starting position and then crunch to the opposite side.\n
4. Repeat until the set is complete.</string>

    <string name="planks_desc">1. Get into a push up position, with your elbows under your shoulders and your feet hip-width apart.\n
2. Bend your elbows and rest your weight on your forearms and on your toes, keeping your body in a straight line.\n
3. Hold for as long as possible.</string>

    <string name="squats_desc">1. Stand up with your feet shoulder-width apart.\n
2. Bend your knees, press your hips back and stop the movement once the hip joint is slightly lower than the knees.\n
3. Press your heels into the floor to return to the initial position.\n
4. Repeat until set is complete.</string>

    <string name="donkey_kick_desc">1. Get down on all fours and position your hands under your shoulders and your knees under your hips.\n
2. Kick back with one leg and squeeze the glutes.\n
3. Bend the knee, lower the leg, and repeat.\n
4. Switch legs.</string>

    <string name="leg_lift_desc">1. Start on all fours with the hands under the shoulders and the knees under the hips.\n
2. Extend one leg behind you.\n
3. Lift the leg to hip level and then slowly lower it back down.\n
4. Repeat with the opposite leg until the set is complete.</string>

    <string name="fire_hydrant_desc">1. Get down on your hands and knees, with your wrists under your shoulders and your knees hip-width apart.\n
2. Keeping the knee bent, raise one leg up and out to the side, until it’s level with your hip.\n
3. Return to the starting position, repeat, and then switch legs.</string>

</resources>